Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we were set to open for Iron Frill,
but while we focused on making a big impact,
Shiori, the leader of Iron Frill, threw us all for a loop by trying to recruit Ai to join her group!
No way, sister! Ai is staying with us, and that's all there is to it!
We totally nailed our performance, and then Shiori had the nerve to declare us rivals on live TV!
If that's how she wants to play it, then we're game for revenge!
Let's go, go, go!
Hello! Good morning, everyone!
Uh, and a good morning to you, Lily!
I'm happy to see all your smiling faces!
Although, one of you looks a little bit on the frowny side today!
Me? This is just the way my face was...
Speak up, Kotaro! And remember to enunciate!
Enunciate? What is her deal?
Yeah, what's up, Lily?
Here's the sitch. I want to shine bright! Time for me to step up my game!
We're already hosting a radio show, the Saga Arena concert was a hit,
and Iron Frill declared us to be their rivals!
You've all been working hard to take revenge, which is awesome!
But I want to show up those girls, too!
I thought if I did something extra amazing to showcase my magicalness,
it would take Franjushu to the next level!
For a tiny little thing, you've got plenty of moxie.
So that's it. I've noticed that Lily has had something pressing on her mind lately.
She's been plotting.
You've got my full support!
Do you have something fun planned?
You know it! Check this out!
For the first time ever, Franjushu is gonna move away from the local Saga TV spotlight
onto a national television network program!
Wait! National TV?!
Yeah! This is what I'm talking about!
I'll be entering as a contestant on Japan's Got Performance!
It's a freestyle-type audition show where anything goes!
First competitors from all over the country compete in the regional preliminaries!
If you win there, then you get to enter the national finals held in Tokyo!
Franjushu will finally have a chance to make our big national debut on television!
Yay!
Lily is an expert when it comes to this sort of stuff.
Yeah! You're gonna win that thing for sure!
I'm crazy stoked!
So when does the show start filming?
It's starting right now!
Yay!
I know the trick to get them to work.
Sakura is a natural. I bet she cheered like this for Ai.
She certainly was a lucky girl with all those fans.
Oh, wow. You're one of the girls from Franshushu, aren't you?
That Saga Arena show was intense.
Oh, thank you. And hopefully, I'll do a great job tonight, too.
Excuse-moi. Clear a path for the talent. Thank you ever so much.
I'm Light Ozura. I am honored to be performing alongside each of you today.
No freaking way! The famous child actor?
What a cutie!
Never heard of him.
Who is he?
Oh, wow. That boy's an excellent television actor.
Pretty famous, too. Kind of reminds me of Lily before she died and came back.
What's a famous child actor doing in a regional competition in Saga?
Oh, hey! You're all members of the idol group Franshushu, right?
You've heard of us?
Of course. I saw that Iron Frill called you out as rivals, so you must be amazing on stage.
I just knew I'd run into you if I came to Saga.
This is great!
So, are you competing as a team today?
Just me. The rest came by for moral support.
It's a pleasure. Let's have fun!
Back at ya. The pleasure is all mine.
What the hell were you thinking? How dare you put me in the same room as those peons?
They're beneath me. This is not how you treat a star.
I'm sorry. This is my fault. I'll speak with the stage manager right away.
Good. Enough. What am I even paying you for, moron?
What the hell is this crap?
My social media profile clearly states that I'll only eat the pudding roll cakes from Semplees.
Saga doesn't have Semplees.
And Saga can kiss my ass.
But, I guess that's why I came to this dumb town in the first place.
None of these yokels have enough talent to outperform me.
Just watch. All I have to do is go on that stage and I'll guarantee myself a trip to the finals.
What about that one girl?
She's a member of Franshushu and they're pretty hot right now.
Ishimura!
Yes, sir?
Do you honestly think I'm worried about some hick-pop group?
To that stupid brain of your stuff, rookie Amy, I plan to win this fail group.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll have those judges in the palm of my hands crying their eyes out.
He is mean!
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the show.
We're on the hunt, searching high and low for Saga's diamonds in the rough.
Let's get things started by welcoming our judges!
Whoa dang, this is way different than local TV.
Everything is so glamorous and over the top on the bigger stage.
Light said all that?
Yeah.
I mean, like, he's a total brat.
And he's got some sort of plan to win.
The only reason he came here is because he thinks he's above everyone so he's sure to
move on.
Oh well.
I'm not worried about him.
I'm gonna do great.
I'm off!
Wish me luck!
Finally, we've been waiting on you to start our cheering section.
We got held up.
I'm sorry.
Please welcome entry number 13, Kotaro Tatsumi!
Huh?
So what type of performance do you plan to share with us today?
Well, it's an impersonation?
I love a good impersonation.
It's a mudskipper during mating season?
Uh...
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Lily has to follow that act?
And now for our next contestant,
the singing sensation from Franz Shushu, number six!
Go get him!
Yeah!
Number six!
Hello.
Before I start,
I would like to thank everybody for taking the time to join us today,
all the way out here in Sokka for this special show.
The world is ever-changing, but the ties that bind families together
and the love they share for one another will always stay the same.
My story today begins with such a family.
A skilled craftsman named Kuma, his wife, and their son come again.
It's no bother.
Go on, keep the change.
It'll be our little secret.
Are you sure about that?
I've always known you to be a little bit of a Benny Bencher.
I've gotten better with age.
You mean he didn't drink at all last night?
Yeah, Mom!
Pa's trying hard to overcome his bad habits,
and he's doing much better!
And he's always asking about you and everything.
I think he still...
He still loves you!
You keep this family together,
just like a nail.
So that must be the reason you worked me over good
with that hammer yesterday.
Dang it, the pipsqueaks got me teary-eyed
and crying like a baby.
She's such a talented actor!
I've never been this moved in my entire life!
Hey, Light!
Good luck out there!
Thanks for warming the crowd up for me.
And now we've reached our final competitor for round one!
You know him, you love him!
Give it up for the famous child actor, Light Ozura!
Come on down!
You must never give up!
Huh?
You can do it!
Keep it up!
You're doing great!
That's it!
Come on, come on!
You've got this!
It's okay!
Don't sweat!
Come on!
You can do it!
I won't leave a paper you!
You must never give up!
Never give up!
You can do it!
Just as planned!
the judges have handed over the tallied scores moving on to round two no surprise light ozona
and number six from fran shushu the showdown's coming up right after these messages
they're both singing for the final round i bet that light has it in the bag then man it seems like
everyone's convinced that this light chump's gonna take the win in advance it did get the audience
riled up or lily life i used to sing this all the time with my papa he said it was one of mommy's
favorites too sizing up your competition no i actually thought you did a great job but
not gonna give up either i'm gonna sparkle that little show you put on it was so lame and outdated
i'm almost embarrassed for you i could say the same about your act yeah right you know i could be on
broadway someday wait on broadway oh are you surprised by that whatever most child actors
don't think about their futures they only think about how cute and tiny they are right now but no
one gives a rat's ass about that stuff when you get older and you're gonna grow up whether you like
it or not so you better have a plan that's why i'll succeed my acting skills are impeccable
and i've got the drive that it takes i won't fade away as i age i'm going to be a legendary actor someday
i'm gonna prove that to this crowd so keep up your pathetic little act while you can and watch me blow
you out of the water
hey lily are you okay yeah i'm fine they're just words so they don't hurt me
i'm gonna win this for franz shushu and then we'll finally get our revenge we're pulling for you out
there i believe in you lily you can do it
the preliminary performances were outstanding i hear you'll be singing this time around i can't wait
oh no this can't be happening that little boy stole lily's song okay but why is that such a bad thing
if lily sings the exact same song the audience will think she's trying to copy him
if that happens her chances of winning are slim to none
what should i do papa what should i do somebody tell me what to do we're pulling for you out there
my acting skills are impeccable and i've got the drive that it takes i can do this
for franz shushu
i will sparkle
i don't know how anyone could follow that it was fantastic we still have another finalist left to
perform though
is this the same song it's a new arrangement
i
so
Shubi do oczywiście tu do o o
pa pa shubi do o pa ya
Shubi do pa pa pa ra pa pa
Shubi do o da ya
Su do be pa
Su do be pa ra pa pa
Pa pon deim pa pa
Shutubi pas bi pa rari pa bie pa ya
Shubi do be doi parapo
Pa ra po fa Ra pa ra pa
Shubi shubi doi parapong
Pa pa ra po pa pa ra po
Pa pa diwi ni skibi ni bibi
Pa ni a pa pa pa ni a mam pa pa
Pa pa YAYAY
WOO!
I knew you could do it!
Wow! Thanks!
Stellar job. Did you improvise that song?
I'm floored by your whole performance.
What did you think when you found out
you were both going to sing the same song?
I remembered my very best friends in front, Shushu.
We've been through a lot,
and there were times we didn't think we could keep going.
But during those bad times, we were always there for each other.
Because of that, we knew we could never give up.
It reminded me that I couldn't give up either.
I knew I had to put on an amazing performance and shine brightly.
That way everyone knows how amazing Franshushu is, too.
You should both be proud of your performances today,
but the rules of the show state that only one of you
can be selected as the winner.
So let's get right to it then, shall we?
This performer proved they had the most star power
and moved us all the tears.
The accomplished child actor, Light Ozura!
Congratulations! You're the winner!
Well done! Way to go, Light!
Light, where are you?
This isn't funny! Come out now!
We're gonna miss our flight if we don't hurry!
No way I could have done that.
I'm a loser.
I might have won the contest,
but I failed as a performer.
You should be proud of yourself, Light!
Did you come to mock me?
I didn't win the contest.
Why would I mock you?
The judges liked your performance better.
That's showbiz for ya.
Besides, I thought you were gonna make a splash on Broadway.
And you're the one that said to never give up, right?
Hey, this is the boys' bathroom.
It's no big deal.
It's only the two of us in here.
No matter what,
I'm always going to twinkle and sparkle.
The girls in Front Shushu will too.
We're going to shine like stars forever.
That's why I'm here today.
I thought if I won the contest
that it would help the group stand out even more.
But Light, you have something I could never have.
Cheer up!
You have a dream.
And it will come true.
Thanks for the pep talk.
You should drop by Tokyo sometime.
Maybe we'll be able to work on something together.
See ya.
Lily here! I hope we can make our dreams come true one day!
All you have to do is work hard and do your best and you'll twinkle like a star!
Next time on Episode 6 of Zombieland Saga Revenge!
Walking Bat Saga! Be there!